shopwittmore.com 2017-09-12

# Privacy Policy – WITTMORE

This Site utilizes a 128-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encrypted checkout to protect personal data. We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information with other parties. WITTMORE LLC may collect and use Users personal information to complete order transactions, process payments, send periodic emails and newsletters, improve customer service, respond to customer service requests, personalize the user experience, run promotional contests and surveys, and to otherwise operate this site’s outlined services. Users may be asked to provide where appropriate their name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information and other relevant information. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the above outlined site services. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf.

Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously.

OPT-IN MAILING LIST AND NEWSLETTER

If a User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, and related product or service information. If at any time a User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

COMMENTS, USER FEEDBACK AND OTHER CONTENT SUBMISSIONS

Additional content a User submits to WITTMORE LLC in any format or delivery method including comments, on-site comments or feedback, content ideas, suggestions, contest entries or any other materials, you agree that WITTMORE LLC may, at any time use your submissions in any medium without restrictions.

NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers’ utilized and other similar information. We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners.

WEB BROWSER COOKIES

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

ADDITIONAL QUESTIONS

Users may contact WITTMORE LLC for any reason regarding the above privacy policy by emailing 

[info@shopwittmore.com](mailto:info@shopwittmore.com) or by mailing a letter to WITTMORE LLC 8236 W 3rd St Los Angeles, CA 90048.CHANGES TO OUTLINED TERMS, CONDITIONS, AND POLICIES

WITTMORE LLC has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

This Terms, Conditions, and Policies page was last updated on February 25, 2015.
